What was my first fulcrum?
我的第一个支点是什么？
The mesenteric artery.
肠系膜动脉。
First fulcrum, one.
第一个支点，一。
Second fulcrum,
第二个支点，
the left colic flexure, it is fixed.
左结肠角，它是固定的。
Third fulcrum,
第三个支点，
I am deep here.
我在这里很深。
And the last point,
最后一个点，
is here.
在这里。
So my intestine, in fact, does this.
所以我的肠子，实际上，它是这样运动的。
In the opposite direction.
反方向。
I place myself there, and in fact the movement is like this.
我把自己放在那里，实际上运动是这样的。
Do you see what I mean?
你明白我的意思吗？
I am now entering a tissue of motility.
我现在进入了一个运动组织。
I can begin to trace a history.
我可以开始讲述一个故事。
I am immediately drawn to the stomach, the spleen, and the left colic flexure.
我立刻被吸引到胃、脾脏和左结肠角。
Its fulcrum is occupied.
它的支点被占据了。
to rebalance a rather deep psychic plane.
重新平衡一个相当深层的心理层面。
Perhaps it is still searching for another fulcrum.
也许他还在寻找另一个支点。
We will bring it to a more anterior fulcrum.
我们将把它带到一个更靠前的支点。
It will rediscover information in its dreams.
他会在梦中找到信息。
It is in this balance between this aortic plane and this
他处于主动脉平面和脾脏平面之间的平衡中。
splenic plane.
脾脏。
It is a plane of integration, of the unconscious that wants to return to the surface
这是一个整合的平面，潜意识想要浮出水面
and which can express itself as a dream or a nightmare.
并可能以梦或噩梦的形式表达。
I place it on the left side.
我把它放在左侧。
to have a fulcrum, to have this freedom here.
为了有一个支点，为了在这里获得这种自由。
And then, the final point is placed here.
然后，终点在这里。
Normally, the epigastric tension should be slightly greater
通常，上腹部张力应略高于
than the hypogastric tension.
下腹部张力。
Always a search for abdominal normotension or abdominal hypotension.
总是寻求腹部正常张力或腹部低张力。
In my palpation, if the hypogastric tension is superior to
在我的触诊中，如果下腹部张力高于
my epigastric tension,
我的上腹部张力，
I am rather in a system of...
我更倾向于一个...系统。
Then either I must work within a system of viscerospatial rebalancing or
那么，我必须在一个内脏空间或流体重新平衡的系统中工作。
fluidic.
流体。
Anything that is hypertension, I must release the fluids.
所有高血压，我必须释放液体。
Anything that is in hypotension, I have a slackening.
所有低血压，我有一个放松。
Therefore, I must reintegrate the viscerospatial system, meaning I must restore the dynamics, increase
所以我必须重新整合内脏空间系统，也就是说，我必须恢复动力，增加
the force.
力量。
This entire ascending colon here, normally, there are still small excesses,
这里所有的升结肠，通常情况下，仍然有一些小的过剩，
small dietary verdicts, can still be improved.
一些小的饮食判断，仍然可以改善。
let's say. When I ascend here, I have an angle that goes like this and I descend again, I descend
我们可以说。当我回到这里时，我有一个这样的角度，然后我下降，我下降
into my zone of joy or, if not resolved, into the zone
进入我的喜悦区，或者，如果问题没有解决，进入
of my anger. When I descend here,
我的愤怒区。当我下降到这里时，
the transverse colon here, it represents my certainties in life or, if
这里的横结肠，它代表着我生活中的确定性，或者，如果
I have not
我没有解决它们，
resolved them, my doubts. When I ascend here,
我的疑虑。当我回到这里时，
I represent, the ascent here represents the zone
我代表，这里的上升代表着
of confidence.
信任区。
or of my anxieties.
或者我的焦虑。
The angle zone here, it is called the culprit's burden.
这里的角度区域，这被称为罪犯的枷锁。
The culprit's burden, that's what needs to be released.
罪犯的枷锁，这就是需要清除的东西。
Here, it's the entire zone here, then when I descend again here,
这里，这是整个区域，然后当我下降到这里时，
I call that the search for my independence.
我称之为寻求我的独立。
I must be totally free from my parents.
我必须完全摆脱我的父母。